Privacy Policy
--------------

This Privacy Policy (the “**Privacy Policy**“) forms part of, and should be read in conjunction with, the Terms of Service and adopts the definitions used therein.

Please read this document as We take the privacy of our Users seriously and We are committed to safeguarding the personal information that You provide Us whilst using the Website and Chaty product?, and We would like to assure You that We are not going to misuse any of the aforesaid information. 

If You have any questions about Our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

**Information We Collect About You**

1. In General. We may collect personal information that can identify You, such as Your name, email address, and other information that does not identify You (like Google Analytics data). When You provide personal information through the Website, the information may be sent to servers located in various countries around the world.
2. Information You Provide. We may collect and store any personal information You enter or upload on the Website or provide to Us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as Your name, email address and, if you transact business with Us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information), image and/or audio files uploaded by You; We also may request information about Your interests and activities, Your gender and age, and other demographic information. We may also collect certain additional information that can be used to identify you, such as your usage data in relation to Chaty and other information we deem relevant for the purpose of providing the Services.
3. Information Collected from Visitors to Your Websites using Chaty’s Services. Whenever a visitor visits Your website, We may also collect and store information from them regarding his/her use of that website such as pages visited, links clicked, non-sensitive text entered, and mouse movements, as well as information more commonly collected such as his/her IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, Internet Service Provider and any other information from the visitor regarding his.her use of Your website and more (“**Visitors’ Information**“) . The Visitors’ Information may in the aggregate identify the visitor however We will not identify him/her as he/she browses the website if he/she turns off cookies. For clarification, when a visitor visits Your website, Your privacy policy applies instead of this Privacy Policy, although You are required to disclose Your ability to collect and review information as described in this Policy. You hereby confirm that You have been granted permission to collect the Visitors’ Information from the users of your website. Chaty shall bear no liability for any damages arising from claim regarding the collection of data from the visitors of Your Website
4. Use of Cookies and Other Technologies to Collect Information. We use various technologies to collect information from Your computer/device and about Your activities on the Website in addition to public information collected from Your website.
    1. Information Collected Automatically. We automatically collect information from Your device and/or browser when You use or visit the Website. This information includes IP address, Your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that Your browser previously accepted from Us and the referring website address. 
    2. Information regarding Your Location. We may, after receiving Your consent by responding to a notification sent to You, collect information regarding Your GPS-based geographic location. Such geographic information will only be collected whilst the Website is running. 
    3. Cookies. When You visit the Website, We may assign Your computer/device one or more cookies, to facilitate access to the Website and to personalize Your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, We also may automatically collect information about Your online activity on the Website, such as the web pages You visit, the links You click, and the searches You conduct on the Website. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but You can usually modify Your browser setting to decline cookies. If You choose to decline cookies, please note that You may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on the Website.
    4. Other Technologies. We may use standard internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track Your use of the Website. We also may include web beacons in promotional email messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information We obtain in this manner enables Us to customise the services We offer visitors to the Website to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of Our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.
    5. Information Collected by Third Parties. We may allow third parties, including Our authorised service providers, advertising companies and ad networks, to display advertisements on the Website. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Unless expressly stated otherwise, the Website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

If you are a Chaty User, We may use information that We collect about You to:

1. Provide the Services on the Website and to improve Users’ experience and the services offered to them;
2. Manage Your Account and provide You with customer support with respect to the Website;
3. Perform research and analysis about Your use of, or interest in, Our products, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
4. Communicate with You by email, postal mail and/or by other ways about products or services that may be of interest to You either from Us, or other third parties;
5. Develop and display content and advertising tailored to Your interests on the Website and other sites or applications;
6. Enforce Our terms of use;
7. Manage Our business; 
8. Process transactions between You and Chaty; 
9. Perform functions as otherwise described to You at the time of collection;  
    If you are a visitor to a website that uses Chaty, We may use Your information to:
10. Enhance or improve the User experience, our Website, or Chaty;
11. Monitor data to ensure that it complies with our Terms of Use;
12. Perform any other function that We believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Website or Chaty.

**With Whom We Share Your Information**

We want You to understand when and with whom We may share personal or other information We have collected about You or Your activities on the Website or while using Our services.

Personal information. We do not share Your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform You and give You an opportunity to opt out of having Your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

1. Authorised Service Providers: We may share Your personal information with Our authorised service providers that perform certain services on Our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting the Website functionality and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through the Website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes;
2. Business Partners: To the extent any personal information is contained in any content or place on the Website, or in any other comment or other User submission, such information when You make purchases, reservations or engage in promotions offered through the Website or Our services, We may share personal information with the businesses with which We partner to offer You those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. Direct Mail Partners. From time to time We may share Our postal mailing list with selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to You; 
3. Other Situations. We also may disclose Your information\* In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise Our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, We may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to Us, in Our sole discretion;  
    \* When We believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, report or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of the Company, Our Users, Our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce the Website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.  
    \* In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of Our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of Your personal information once We have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If You want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage You to visit the websites of those third parties.

Aggregated and non-personal information. We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may combine non-personal information We collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, We may tell Our advertisers the number of visitors to the Website and the most popular features or Service accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop content and service that we hope You and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

**Third-Party Sites**

There are a number of places on the Website or through Our services where You may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if You click on an advertisement, a third party’s content or a search result on the Website, You may be taken to a website that We do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information from You and, in some instances, provide Us with information about Your activities on those websites. We recommend that You consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites You visit by clicking on the “privacy” link typically located at the bottom of the webpage You are visiting. 

**Your Choices About Collection and Use of Your Information**

You can choose not to provide Us with certain information, but that may result in You being unable to use certain features of the Website because such information may be required in order for You to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; post a comment; or initiate other transactions on the Website.

When You register on the Website We may send You emails and/or newsletters about Service updates, improvements, special offers, or containing special distributions of content by Us. At any time You can choose to no longer receive commercial or promotional emails or newsletters from Us by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE link at the bottom of any email message from Chaty. You also will be given the opportunity, in any commercial email that We send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for Us to process an opt-out request. We may send You other types of transactional and relationship email communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices and surveys. Please note that changing information in Your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or communications from Us. If We have already provided Your information to a third party before You have changed Your preferences or updated Your information, You may have to change You preferences directly with that third party.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard Your personal information from unauthorised access and disclosure. 

We want You to feel confident using the Website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although We take steps to secure Your information, We do not promise, and You should not expect, that Your personal information, searches or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email.

**Access to information**

The Data Protection Act gives You the right to access information held about You. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Data Protection Act. 

**No Rights of Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.

**Data retention**

The right of erasure: Our users can delete their account themselves from the interface (if they are not on a paid plan), or send us a request to delete their account and all the information related to it by contacting us through our [contact form](https://chaty.app/contact/).  
The data of your account is stored on our end as long as the account is active.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in Our practices and services. When We post changes to this Privacy Policy, We will revise the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If We make any material changes in the way We collect, use and/or share Your personal information, We will notify You by sending an email to the email address You most recently provided Us in Your Account, profile or registration (unless We do not have such an email address), and/or by sending a push notification or posting notice of the changes on the Website. We recommend that You check the Website from time to time to inform Yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of Our other policies.

**GDPR**

Read more on our [GDPR page](https://chaty.app/gdpr/) 

**How to Contact Us**

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Our information-handling practices or if You would like to request information about Our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact Us through the [contact page](https://chaty.app/contact/)

Sign Up to Chaty
----------------

Integrating Chaty into your website takes less than 2 minutes. Sign up now and start communicating with your visitors on their favorite chat platforms

[Sign Up for Free

](https://go.chaty.app/register)

30-Day Refund Policy | Cancel Anytime

© 2024 Chaty. All rights reserved.

Company
-------

Resources
---------

Product
-------
